How's your eyesight?
你的视力怎么样？
From the moment we're born, our eyes grow, our vision becomes clearer and some of us will have normal or even 20:20 vision.
从出生的那一刻起，我们的眼睛就会不断发育，视力会变得越来越清晰，有些人会拥有正常甚至是2.0的视力。
However, others will become short-sighted and end up wearing glasses or contact lenses to help them see everything clearly.
但另一些人则会患上近视，最终需要戴上眼镜或隐形眼镜才能看清事物。
And some experts claim that more of us will be wearing them in the future because of our lifestyle when we were younger.
一些专家称，由于我们年轻时的生活方式，未来会有更多人需要佩戴矫正视力的眼镜。
Even today, optometrists are reporting a rise in short-sightedness – also called myopia – in children.
即便是现在，验光师们也指出儿童患近视眼的比率正在上升。
The condition can be genetic, but it's also partly being blamed on a number of modern-day factors – particularly children staring at phone screens, computers and game consoles for long periods of time.
近视可能与遗传有关，但也有部分原因要归咎于多种现代因素——尤其是儿童长时间盯着手机屏幕、电脑和游戏机。
It's believed myopia also makes them susceptible to secondary eye conditions such as glaucoma, retinal detachment and other visual impairments later in life.
有观点认为，近视还会让他们在日后更容易患上继发性眼部疾病，比如青光眼、视网膜脱落以及其他视力损伤问题。
Of course, children have had increased screen time due to lockdowns imposed during the Covid pandemic – it's been the only way to access education and communicate with others.
当然，新冠疫情期间的封锁措施导致儿童的屏幕使用时间有所增加——这曾是他们接受教育和与他人沟通的唯一途径。
But education generally could be blamed for the rise in myopia.
但总体而言，教育也可能是近视率上升的一个诱因。
Neema Ghorbani-Mojarrad, lecturer at the University of Bradford, told BBC Future website: "We suspect it is reading and spending more time indoors.
布拉德福德大学讲师妮玛·戈尔巴尼-莫加拉德在接受BBC未来频道采访时表示：“我们猜测原因在于阅读以及长时间待在室内。
Every year of education completed increases the expected amount of short-sightedness."
所受教育每增加一年，近视的概率就会相应上升。”
The problem appears to be more severe in some Asian countries.
这个问题在一些亚洲国家似乎更为严重。
Some experts say that in these places with huge educational success, children spend more time indoors studying.
有专家表示，在这些教育成就斐然的地区，儿童会花更多时间在室内学习。
Therefore, it seems, spending more time outdoors could be good for children's eye health.
因此，多待在户外或许有益于儿童的眼部健康。
The UK's College of Optometrists is suggesting parents should get their kids playing outside for two hours a day.
英国验光师学院建议家长每天让孩子在户外玩耍两小时。
Several scientific studies show this can prevent or stop the development of myopia.
多项科学研究表明，这样做能够预防或阻止近视的产生。
There's been a focus on using technology, such as laser surgery, for fixing myopia, but for children at least, it seems a dose of daylight and a break from the screen might be part of the solution.
目前人们很关注用激光手术等技术来矫正近视，但至少对于儿童来说，似乎多接触日光、远离屏幕或许应该是一部分解决方案。
Opticians also recommend kids have regular eye tests to identify any problems before they become more severe.
配镜师还建议，儿童应定期进行视力检查，以便在眼部问题恶化之前及时发现。